http://www.londomondo.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy effective from May 1st 2017
Table Of ContentsOur Commitment To PrivacyThe Information We CollectHow We Use InformationOur Commitment To Data SecurityHow To Contact Us Our Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. The Information We CollectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the myhardtail.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:NameMailing AddressEmailPhone numberBirthdayCredit/Debit Card InformationProduct informationWe also collect aggregate use data through Google Analytics.
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of www.myhardtail.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA.
We also use Pinterest's Conversion Tracking Pixel. This allows us to track sales associated with people who used Pinterest to discover our products.
The Way We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How To Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (773) 404-1593 or send us an email at sales@londomondo.com.
Subscribe Sign up to get the latest on sales, new releases and more …
